Redwood Canyon Ramblers collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Event recordings and related materials
  - Home demo love songs, Berkeley, California - Janet Smith, 1959, AFC 2011/011: SR23
    - Sound recording (cut-level), js1959t01.aif - js1959t13.aif; 13 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Three Ravens" 00:02:31
      "Blow The Candles Out" 00:02:04
      "Young Heart" 00:01:48
      "My Only Joy And Dearie O" 00:02:39
      "The Waters Of Tyne" 00:01:41
      "Bonny George Campbell" 00:01:08
      "Come All You Fair And Tender Ladies" 00:01:55
      "Come To The Garden" 00:05:22
      "I Gave My Love A Cherry" 00:01:19
    - Song list and production notes for SR23, November 5, 2011, js1959demo.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Photographs of tape box interior, with song lists, 1959, Barton Reel Number 55 tape box-1.jpg, Barton Reel Number 55 tape box-2.jpg; 2 photographs: black and white, digital (.txt)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, September 1959, December 26, 1959, February 1960, AFC 2011/011: SR02
    - Sound recording (full), AFC 2011/011: SR02; RXJ 0531; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; Side 1: 00:42:24, Side 2: 00:31:59): analog, 7 1/2 ips, mono; 7 in.
      Original Rosenberg inventory number: tape 13.
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rcr1959kpfa01.aif - rcr1959kpfa18.aif, rcr1959kre01.aif - rcr1959kre10.aif, rcr1960kre01.aif - rcr1960kre04.aif; 32 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      KPFA Studios (September 1959)
      Demo/audition tape; produced by Gert Charito.
      "Mountain Fling" medley: "Wildwood Flower"/"Rosewood Casket"/"Cindy"/"Woody's Rag" 00:03:57
      "Salty Dog" 00:02:08
      KRE Studios (December 26, 1959)
      KRE Studios (February 1960)
      "Home Sweet Home" [the song cuts off abruptly] 00:01:24
      "Auld Lang Syne" 00:03:14
      "Where The Soul Never Dies" 1 [breakdown; with Audrey Smith on vocals; the performance stops abruptly] 00:01:01
      "Where The Soul Never Dies" 2 [breakdown; with Audrey Smith on vocals; the performance stops abruptly again] 00:00:52
    - Song list and production notes for SR02, January 7, 2011, 1959_1960StudioSessions (Reel 13).txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Handwritten song list, with counter numbers from the tape deck, undated, rcr1959_1960StudioSessions.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
  - Royal Recording Studio session, Berkeley, California - Scott Hambly and Mayne Smith, February 1960, AFC 2011/011: SR30
    - Sound recording (cut-level), shms1960-02-00t01.aif - shms1960-02-00t04.aif; 4 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Home Sweet Home" 00:01:24
      "Old Lang Syne" 00:03:14
      "Where The Soul Never Dies" #1 (breakdown) - Audrey Smith on vocals 00:01:01
      "Where The Soul Never Dies" #2 - Audrey Smith on vocals [recording abruptly ends] 00:00:52
    - Song list and production notes for SR30, January 7, 2011, shms1960-02-00.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
  - Jam session with Frank Miller and John Schuler, Gambier, Ohio - Neil Rosenberg, April 1960, AFC 2011/011: SR31
    - Sound recording (cut-level), nvr1960-04-00t01.aif - nvr1960-04-00t13.aif; 13 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      SR31 includes tracks 13-31 from Rosenberg inventory tape 16.
      Neil Rosenberg (banjo); Frank Miller (banjo, guitar)
      "Foggy Mountain Breakdown" 00:02:00
      "Dear Old Dixie" [glitch on source tape towards end] 00:02:24
      "Little Rosewood Casket" 00:01:20
      "Earl's Breakdown" 00:01:35
      "Farewell Blues" 00:01:17
      Neil Rosenberg (banjo, guitar, vocals); Franklin Miller (guitar, fiddle, vocals); John Schuler (banjo, vocals)
      "Bowling Green" 00:02:01
      "Old Mountain Dew" [fragment] 00:00:25
      "Old Mountain Dew" 00:04:05
      "Orange Blossom Special" 00:03:04
      "Smith" 00:01:38
      "Pike County Breakdown" 00:02:35
      "Uncle Pen" 00:02:02
      "Rabbit In A Log" 00:03:27
    - Song list and production notes for SR31, January 2, 2013, nvr1960-04-00.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Song list and production notes for Rosenberg inventory tape 16, undated, NVR ReelNumber16 Notes.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
    - Notes for Rosenberg inventory tape 16, undated, rcrNVRNumber16A.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
    - Tape box and handwritten notes for Rosenberg inventory tape 16, undated, rcrNVRNumber16box.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
  - Royal Recording Studio session, Berkeley, California - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, July 13, 1960, AFC 2011/011: SR32
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rcr1960-07-13t01.aif - rcr1960-07-13t12.aif; 12 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Cripple Creek" 00:02:21
      "Snow Dove" #1 [with false start] 00:03:22
      "Snow Dove" #2 00:03:41
      "Molly And Tenbrooks" #1 [with tuning intro] 00:02:47
      "Molly And Tenbrooks" #2 [with tuning and banter intro] 00:02:53
      "Swanee" [with tuning and banter intro] 00:02:39
      "Home Sweet Home" #1 [fast tempo, cuts in] 00:01:13
      "Home Sweet Home" #2 [with vocal intro] 00:02:22
      "Orange Blossom Special" #1 [with tuning and banter intro] 00:03:34
      "Orange Blossom Special" #2 [with rowdy banter intro] 00:03:41
      "Smith" #1 [discussion and off-mic run through twice] 00:02:40
      "Smith" #2 [on-mic/tape runs out] 00:01:04
    - Song list and production notes for SR32, March 27, 2011, rcr1960-07-13.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Scott Hambly's notes, undated, Scotts notes 7-13-60.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Tape reel, undated, rcr1960-07-13.pdf; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.pdf)
  - Royal Recording Studio session, Berkeley, California - Redwood Canyon Ramblers, June 9, 1961, AFC 2011/011: SR33
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rcr1961-06-09t01.aif - rcr1961-06-09t06.aif; 6 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Little Maggie" 00:02:23
      "Rawhide" 00:02:46
      "House Carpenter" 00:02:22
      "Rocky Run" 00:02:57
      "Cry From The Cross" 00:02:49
      "Banjolina" 00:02:45
    - Song list and production notes for SR33, March 27, 2011, rcr1961-06-09.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Mayne Smith's comments, undated, rcr1961-06-09-Maynes comments.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Tape reel, undated, rcr1961-06-09.pdf; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.pdf)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers at Hotel Shattuck, Berkeley, California, August 23, 1961, AFC 2011/011: SR34
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rcr1961-08-23t01.aif - rcr1961-08-23t08.aif; 8 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      Introduction by Don Hambly and Campbell Coe 00:08:01
      "Jesse James" 00:02:55
      "Hard Times" 00:03:12
      "Across The Blue Mountains" - Janet Smith and Rita Weill 00:03:23
      "Delia" - Janet Smith and Rita Weill 00:02:57
      "Yad Anuga" - Janet Smith and Rita Weill 00:02:51
      "Mocking Banjo" 00:03:45
      "The Wreck Of The Old '97" [with outro thank yous] 00:03:16
    - Song list and production notes for SR34, March 27, 2011, rcr1961-08-23.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers and the Carroll County Boys (Vern & Ray) at The Washington School, December 2, 1961, AFC 2011/011: SR03
    - Sound recording (full), AFC 2011/011: SR03; RXJ 0532; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side 1: 00:44:22, Side 2: 00:44:06): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Recorded in the auditorium at The Washington School, Berkeley, California. Personnel: LaVern Williams, lead tenor and second mandolin; Ray Parks, tenor and fiddle; Gerry Grove, bass; Clyde Williamson, second guitar; Mayne Smith, lead tenor and guitar; Scott Hambly, first mandolin and occasional lead; Pete Berg, banjo and harmony on Redwood Canyon Ramblers tunes. Continued on SR04.
      Original Rosenberg inventory number: tape 14.
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rcr1961-12-02t01.aif - rcr1961-12-02t28.aif; 28 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      Introduction/tuning 00:00:55
      "Crazy Horse" 00:02:38
      "Hit Parade Of Love" [recording flaw for a moment] 00:03:06
      "Little Maggie" 00:03:00
      "I Wonder Where You Are Tonight" 00:03:06
      "Rocky Run" 00:03:37
      "Poison Lies" 00:02:58
      "House Carpenter" 00:03:06
      "Mother's Only Sleeping" 00:04:21
      "Banjo Signal" 00:02:31
      "John Henry"/pitch for the new record release ("Starday EP for sale") 00:05:02
      "Can't You Hear Me Callin'" 00:03:49
      "Banjolina" 00:03:25
      "Arkansas Traveler" [reel direction change] 00:02:44
      "Ruby" ("take your business to Jon Lundberg") 00:03:42
      "Teardrops In Your Eyes" 00:02:47
      "Home Sweet Home" 00:02:33
      "On My Mind" 00:01:57
      Set 2 (part 1)
      Tuning 00:00:58
      "Prisoner's Song" 00:03:27
      "Cabin On The Mountain" [in the documentation as "Cabin On A Mountain"] 00:03:03
      "Banjo Fling" 00:04:12
      "Darling Nellie Across The Sea" 00:05:08
      "Wicked Path Of Sin" [with false start] 00:03:59
      "Blue Ridge Cabin Home" 00:03:08
      "Uncle Pen" ("I'd be seeing Lefty Frizell in Redwood City") 00:03:14
      "Mocking Banjo" 00:02:52
      "She's More To Be Pitied" [reel change] 00:03:38
    - Song list and production notes for SR03, January 5, 2011, rcr1961-12-02.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Typed song list, by tape side, undated, rcr1961-12-02 Reel 14.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
    - Concert flyer, December 2, 1961, carroll_county_low.jpg; 1 graphic image; black and white, digital (.jpg)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers and the Carroll County Boys (Vern & Ray) at The Washington School, December 2, 1961, AFC 2011/011: SR04
    - Sound recording (full), AFC 2011/011: SR04; RXJ 0533; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; Side 1: 00:15:58, Side 2: 00:15:52): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Recorded at The Washington School, Berkeley, California. Continued from SR03; see the notes for further details.
      Original Rosenberg inventory number: tape 15.
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rcr1961-12-02t29.aif - rcr1961-12-02t37.aif; 9 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      Set 2 (part 2)
      "Billy In The Lowlands" 00:03:35
      "Blue Moon Of Kentucky" 00:03:26
      "Rawhide" 00:03:29
      "Footprints In The Snow" 00:02:59
      "Christmas Time's A Comin'" [the song ends abruptly; tape ends; reel direction change] 00:01:35
      "Hard Times" 00:03:39
      "Sweetheart You Done Me Wrong" 00:02:50
      "Sally Jo" 00:02:36
      "Black Mountain Rag" [end of set] 00:02:53
    - Song list and production notes for SR04, January 5, 2011, 1961 December 2 (Reel 14&15).txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Typed song list, undated, rcr1961-12-02 Reel 15.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
  - "Midnight Special" (radio program), KPFA, Berkeley, California - Country Boys, May 12, 1962, AFC 2011/011: SR38
    - Sound recording (cut-level), cb1962-05-12t01.aif - cb1962-05-12t08.aif; 8 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      Introductions/"Salty Dog" 00:02:43
      "Banjo Signal" 00:02:17
      "The Prisoner's Song"/Scott announces upcoming RCR show 00:03:25
      "Way Downtown" 00:02:38
      "Get Up John" 00:03:05
      "Teardrops In My Eyes" 00:02:35
      "When You And I Were Young, Maggie" 00:02:10
      "Muleskinner Blues" 00:02:36
    - Song list and production notes for SR38, April 24, 2012, cb1962-05-12.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
  - Ridgerunners at Sierra Sound Labs, Berkeley, California, June 1962, AFC 2011/011: SR39
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rr1962-06-00t01.aif - rr1962-06-00t08.aif; 8 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Blue Grass Breakdown" 00:02:05
      "Live And Let Live" 00:01:58
      "Under The Double Eagle" 00:02:52
      "Grandfather's Clock" 00:03:44
      "Loving You Too Well" 00:02:04
      "Each Season Changes You" 00:02:27
      "Devil's Dream" 00:02:10
      "Childish Love" 00:02:25
    - Song list and production notes for SR39, February 18, 2013, rr1962-06-00 studio.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Handwritten song list, with counter numbers from the tape deck, undated, rr1962-06 studio.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
      Includes title and performer information for other recordings on the same tape.
  - "Midnight Special" (radio program), KPFA, Berkeley, California - Scott Hambly and friends, July 28, 1962, AFC 2011/011: SR40
    - Sound recording (cut-level), sh1962-07-28t01.aif - sh1962-07-28t03.aif; 3 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Wheel Hoss" - unidentified singer 00:02:22
      "Katy Dear" - unidentified singer 00:01:54
      "Live And Let Live" - unidentified singer 00:02:21
    - Song list and production notes for SR40, February 18, 2013, sh1962-07-28 midnight special.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Handwritten song list, with counter numbers from the tape deck, undated, Reel T-F94.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
      None of the songs listed seem to match the contents of the tape.
  - Ridgerunners at Bear's Lair, Berkeley, California, October 12, 1962, AFC 2011/011: SR41
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rr1962-10-12t01.aif - rr1962-10-12t40.aif; 40 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Will You Be Loving Another Man" 00:02:07
      "Dixie Breakdown" 00:02:20
      "Little Willie" 00:03:07
      "Devil's Dream" 00:02:07
      "Brand New Shoes" 00:02:08
      "Wildwood Flower" 00:02:10
      "Pretty Polly" 00:03:08
      "Shuckin' The Corn" 00:02:41
      "Red Rocking Chair" 00:03:00
      "Dixie Ramble" 00:02:55
      "Molly And Tenbrooks" 00:02:32
      "Grandfather's Clock" 00:03:43
      "Bluegrass Breakdown" [Scott says "welcome back for the 4th set"] 00:02:59
      "Teardrops In My Eyes" 00:02:54
      "Auld Lang Syne" 00:02:59
      "Loving You Too Well" [Scott says it's a repeat] 00:02:48
      "Flop-Eared Mule" 00:02:16
      "Under The Double Eagle" 00:03:28
      "Live And Let Live" 00:02:48
      "Good Woman's Love" 00:03:06
      "Rawhide" 00:02:39
      "Salty Dog" 00:02:25
      "Anchors Aweigh" 00:03:02
      "Little Cabin Home On The Hill" 00:02:51
      "Bugle Call Rag" 00:02:47
      "Is It Too Late Now" 00:02:51
      "Hard Times" 00:03:22
      "Prisoner's Song" 00:02:55
      "Shady Grove" 00:02:16
      "Each Season Changes You" 00:02:29
      "Remington Ride" 00:03:21
      "The Pain In My Heart" 00:03:12
      "Foggy Mountain Breakdown [reel side change]" 00:02:08
      "Swannanoa Tunnel" 00:01:41
      "Earl's Breakdown" 00:02:19
      "Blue Moon Of Kentucky" 00:02:09
      "Bells Of St. Mary's" 00:02:08
      "Little Maggie" 00:02:39
      "Greensleeves" 00:04:07
      "Get Up John" 00:08:28
    - Song list and production notes for SR41, February 18, 2013, rr1962-10-12.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Typed song list, with counter numbers from the tape deck, undated, rr1962-10-12.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
    - Flyer for the Bear's Lair performance, undated, ASUC 4.jpg; 1 graphic image (.jpg)
    - Ridgerunners publicity photo 1, undated, band.bmp; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.bmp)
    - Ridgerunners publicity photo 2, undated, banjo.jpg; 1 photograph: black and white, digital (.jpg)
      Low-resolution copy of a photograph; possibly on paper. Only two members of the group are in the picture
    - "They'll Be Comin' Round The Mountain," October 12, 1962, rr1962-10-12.jpg; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.jpg)
      Newspaper clipping from The Daily Californian
  - Ridgerunners at The Coffee Gallery, San Francisco, California, October 13, 1962, AFC 2011/011: SR42
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rr1962-10-13t01.aif - rr1962-10-13t18.aif; 18 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Rollin' In My Sweet Baby's Arms" 00:02:35
      "Under The Double Eagle" 00:03:18
      "Prisoner's Song" 00:02:56
      "Home Sweet Home" 00:02:44
      "Good Woman's Love" 00:02:50
      "Hard Times" 00:02:59
      "Salty Dog Blues" 00:02:37
      "Wheel Hoss" 00:02:33
      "After Dark" 00:02:21
      "Dixie Ramble" 00:03:07
      "Red Rocking Chair" 00:02:32
      "Cripple Creek" 00:01:46
      "Darling Nellie Gray" 00:02:15
      "Clinch Mountain Backstep" 00:02:10
      "Childish Love" 00:03:02
      "Sweetheart You Done Me Wrong" 00:02:21
      "Anchors Aweigh" [reel side change] 00:02:01
      "Footprints In The Snow" 00:02:24
    - Song list and production notes for SR42, undated, rr1962-10-13.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Front and back covers, plus the insert for the CD Live in San Francisco, by the Ridgerunners, 2013, rr1962-10-13-Front.jpg, rr1962-10-13-Back.jpg, rr1962-10-13-inset.jpg; 3 photographs: color, digital (.jpg)
  - "Folk Music With Rolf Cahn" (radio program), KPFA Berkeley, California - Ridgerunners, 1962, AFC 2011/011: SR35
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rr1962-00-00t01rolfcahn.aif - rr1962-00-00t12rolfcahn.aif; 12 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      Rolf Cahn Introduction 00:01:48
      "Childish Love" 00:02:57
      "Under The Double Eagle"/"what is bluegrass?" 00:04:04
      "Sweetheart You Done Me Wrong" 00:02:56
      "Rawhide" 00:03:23
      "Prisoner's Song"/"why are you in it?" 00:03:20
      "Good Woman's Love"/"the guitar is the orphan?" 00:03:09
      "Little Willie"/"what about the rhythm?" 00:04:33
      Wheel Hoss 00:02:17
      Rolf Cahn summary 00:01:56
      "Red Rocking Chair" - Al Ross and Dave Cohen 00:04:01
      Rolf Cahn's closing/"Brown's Ferry Blues" [fragment/fade out] 00:00:29
    - Song list and production notes for SR35, February 18, 2013, rr1962-00-00rolfcahn.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Typed song list, with counter numbers from the tape deck, undated, rr1962-00-00rolfcahn.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
  - Home recording (location unidentified), Berkeley, California - Ridgerunners, 1962, AFC 2011/011: SR36
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rr1962-00-00t01home.aif - rr1962-00-00t15home.aif; 15 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Molly And Tenbrooks" 00:02:04
      "Footprints In The Snow" [fragment] 00:00:14
      "The Cruel War" 00:02:12
      "Rawhide" #1 [aborted] 00:00:45
      "Rawhide" #2 00:02:30
      "Teardrops In My Eyes" 00:02:07
      "Under The Double Eagle" 00:02:31
      "Wheel Hoss" 00:01:22
      "After Dark" 00:01:45
      "Anchors Aweigh" 00:01:46
      "Chinatown, My Chinatown" [fragment] 00:00:31
      "Little Maggie" 00:01:39
      "Wildwood Flower" 00:02:04
      "Childish Love" 00:02:29
      "White House Blues" [Al Ross solo] 00:00:55
    - Song list and production notes for SR36, February 18, 2013, rr1962-00-00home.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Typed song list, with counter numbers from the tape deck, undated, rr1962-00-00home.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
  - "Midnight Special" (radio program), KPFA, Berkeley, California - Janet Smith, 1962, AFC 2011/011: SR37
    - Sound recording (cut-level), js1962-00-00t01.aif - js1962-00-00t04.aif; 4 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      Archivist's note: The unidentified woman singing on "Well Met" and "Geordie" may be Miriam Stafford or Rita Weill (according to Neil Rosenberg).
      "Well Met" ["House Carpenter"] - Janet Smith and an unidentified woman (duet) 00:04:23
      "Geordie" - Janet Smith and an unidentified woman (duet) 00:03:17
      "Lass Of The Low Country" - Janet Smith 00:03:02
      "Old Maid's Song" - Janet Smith 00:03:10
    - Song list and production notes for SR37, February 18, 2013, js1962-00-00.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Typed song list, with counter numbers from the tape deck, undated, js1962-00-00.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
  - Home recording (possibly made in Norm Cohen's apartment), Berkeley, California - Scott Hambly, Al Ross, and Sandy Rothman, March 15, 1963, AFC 2011/011: SR44
    - Sound recording (cut-level), sh1963-03-15t01.aif - sh1963-03-15t36.aif; 36 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Blue Grass Stomp" 00:02:46
      "Old Folks At Home" 00:03:28
      "My Old Kentucky Home" 00:03:36
      "Country Boy Rock And Roll" 00:00:33
      "Cripple Creek" [fragment] 00:00:08
      "Cripple Creek" [two takes] 00:03:03
      "Cripple Creek" 00:01:57
      "Footprints In The Snow" [with false start] 00:02:59
      "Ruby" 00:02:41
      "Crazy Creek" [two attempts] 00:00:54
      "Red Rocking Chair" 00:02:27
      "Each Season Changes You" 00:02:57
      "Muleskinner Blues" 00:02:21
      "Dill Pickles Rag" 00:02:06
      "Crawdad Song" 00:02:44
      "Good Woman's Love" 00:02:24
      "When You Wore A Tulip" 00:02:00
      "Country Boy Rock And Roll" 00:02:04
      "Roanoke" [with false start] 00:01:31
      "Are You All Alone" #1 [key of A] 00:03:02
      "Are You All Alone" #2 [key of B; reel side change] 00:02:46
      "Are You All Alone" #3 [key of B♭] 00:00:48
      "Under The Double Eagle"/Al leading jam 00:03:46
      "Tragic Romance" 00:03:12
      "Bluebell" [three takes] 00:01:55
      "Sitting On Top Of The World" 00:02:07
      "Live And Let Live" 00:02:08
      Fragment of Clarence White licks/discussion of next tune 00:00:43
      "San Antonio Rose" 00:03:03
      "Scotland" 00:02:51
      Joke tuning/"Tennessee Blues" 00:02:04
      "Wildwood Flower" 00:02:41
      "Billy In The Low Ground" 00:02:17
      "Done Gone" 00:01:36
      "Pike County Breakdown" 00:02:21
      "Auld Lang Syne [with coda]" 00:02:34
    - Song list and production notes for SR44, February 18, 2013, sh1963-03-15.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
    - Handwritten song list, with counter numbers from the tape deck, undated, sh1963-03-15.pdf; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.pdf)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers at The Cabale, Berkeley, California, March 1963, AFC 2011/011: SR43
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rcr1963-03-00t01.aif - rcr1963-03-00t06.aif; 6 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Red Rocking Chair (Sugar Baby)" 00:02:20
      "Goodbye Old Pal" 00:01:53
      "Blue Ridge Cabin Home" 00:02:25
      "Rawhide" [ends with "Moonlight In Vermont" tease] 00:03:17
      "Shady Grove" 00:02:59
      "John Hardy" [set closer with commentary] 00:01:35
    - Song list and production notes for SR43, April 6, 2011, rcr1963-03-00.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers at The Cabale, Berkeley, California, April 4, 1963, AFC 2011/011: SR45
    - Sound recording (cut-level), rcr1963-04-04t01.aif - rcr1963-04-04t06.aif; 6 sound files: high-resolution files, digital (.aif)
      "Let Those Brown Eyes Smile At Me" 00:01:54
      "Banjo Fling (Hamilton County Breakdown)" 00:02:30
      "Childish Love" 00:02:54
      "How Mountain Girls Can Love" 00:02:39
      "Ruby" 00:02:20
      "John Hardy" [set closer with commentary] 00:00:55
    - Song list and production notes for SR45, April 6, 2011, rcr1963-04-04.txt; 1 manuscript: black and white, digital (.txt)
  - Redwood Canyon Ramblers at The Cabale, August 16, 1963, AFC 2011/011: SR05
    - Sound recording (full), AFC 2011/011: SR05; RXJ 0534; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; Side 1: 00:32:19, Side B: 00:28:54): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.